Curriculum Vitae

SUMMARY

I had studied programming while in college, and decided to further develop my programming skills, especially in web programming. I have over 1 years of experience as an Frontend Developer in working and passion for responsive website design and mobile-first design

INFORMATION

Full Name : Akhsan Bayu Riantama

Place, Date of Birth : Jayapura, 3 February 1999

Gender : Male

Address : Jl. Kopeng KM 5, Tegalrejo, Magelang

Email : akhsanby@gmail.com

Phone Number : +62895401224170

EDUCATION

team

STMIK Bina Patria, Kota Magelang - S.Kom

October 2017 - Desember 2021

Graduate as Informatics Engineering student with GPA 3.49 by produce a final assignment about step prediction with AI

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Digireg Indonesia - Frontend Developer
March 2022 – February 2023
☐ Create a WebGIS frontend based on wireframes specified by the client or company
Collaborate with Backend Developers in creating APIs to create responses that match the
needs of Frontend Developer
$\hfill\square$ Revise and create website-based company supporting tools according to company
requests
Mitra Payment Indonesia - Technical Support
July 2023 - December 2023
☐ Helping clients find solutions to payment gateway problems
$\hfill \Box$ Educate new clients on how to use the company's payment gateway platform
☐ Recording bugs on the payment gateway platform to be forwarded to the development

☐ Assisted with several changes to the frontend appearance of the platform indirectly through pull requests on GitHub
EXPERTISE AND SKILLS
Programing Language PHP, Javascript
Framework / Library Laravel, Codelgniter, VueJS, ReactJS
Design Tools Inkscape, Figma
TRAINING & COURSE
Course Coding Online in Dicoding Academy 2020 - 2021
 Learn the basics of HTML and CSS as the pillars of a website. Learn the basics of JavaScript, from the fundamentals, syntax and features of ES6, to the concept of automation tests using popular frameworks. Learn a lot & deeply about JavaScript to make website attractive.
Course Coding Online in Udemy 2023 - Present
Im currently studying Golang : Beginner to Advanced, Laravel : Beginner to Advanced, & NodeJS : Beginner to Advanced with Programmer Zaman Now
Kampus Merdeka with Hacktiv8 August 2021 – February 2022 I learn basic HTML & Css in Kode.id I learn Javascript ES6: Basic to Advance in Kode.id I lean Styling Component ReactJS in Kode.id I learn how to use ReactJS & React Native with reusable components & write clean code
in Kode.id

SOCIAL MEDIA

Github - https://github.com/akhsanby

Portfolio web - https://akhsanby.vercel.app

Linkedin - https://www.linkedin.com/in/akhsanby